Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- A: Mayra Peters-Quintero and Andy Stettner on Tuv Taam Labor Dispute; Oscar Palacios, Richard Greene, Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton / B: Primary Preview with Norm Fruchter, Andy Stettner, Brad Lander, Kathy Goldman; Jonathan Bowles on State Budget Crisis [2001-0171], 2001-09-02; 2001-09-0
  Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton and Richard Green on the 10th anniversary of the Crown Heights riots; Maira Peters-Quintero (PRLDEF attorney), Oscar Palacios (fired worker) and Arieh Lebowitz (Jewish Labor Committee) on the efforts to organize the workers at Tuv Taam in Brooklyn. Co-host, Nan Rubin. Mayoral Primary Show on the issues, with Kathy Goldman (CFRC), Andy Stettner (JFREJ), Norman Fruchter (Institute for Education andf Social Policy, NYU), Brad Lander (Fifth Avenue Committee and ANHD); the New York State Budget with Jonathan Bowls, Center for an Urban Future.
- Tuv Taam Labor Dispute; Crown Heights Riots 10 Years [2001-0136], 2001-09-02; cuid2609 (Box 15, Item 718_0544, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_608)
  Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton and Richard Green on the 10th anniversary of the Crown Heights riots; Maira Peters-Quintero (PRLDEF attorney), Oscar Palacios (fired worker) and Arieh Lebowitz (Jewish Labor Committee) on the efforts to organize the workers at Tuv Taam in Brooklyn.
  Original Format: DAT, Duration 65 min.
- Primary Elections; State Budget Crunch [2001-0135], 2001-09-09; cuid34208 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0543)
- Trembling Before G-d [2001-0180], 2001-09-11; cuid34209 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0327)
  Duration: 1:02:08, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Frequency Background Nosie During Program; High Amount of Buzz During Program; No Right Channel From 00:07:00 Until 00:15:17 on Side B During Program; Phasing During Program; Static During Program
- Amira Habiba Brown, Emily Jacir, Ali Abunimah, Nadia Hijab, 2001-09-16; cuid34210 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0333)
  Duration: 1:53:37, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; High Amount of Hiss During Program
- 1st Anniversary of Intifada with Alisa Solomon, Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark, Phyllis Bennis [2001-0177], 2001 September 24; 2001 September 30; cuid34211 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0324)
  Duration: 1:56:48, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Background Noise During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0542, 718_0535
- First Anniversary of Intifada; Phyllis Bennis on U.S. Foreign Policy and Cold War on Recent Events [2001-0134], 2001-09-24; cuid34212 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0542)
  Duration: 0:58:28, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0324, 718_0535
- First Anniversary of Intifada; Phyllis Bennis on WTC/Pentagon Attacks (Rebroadcast) [2001-0127], 2001-09-30; cuid34213 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0535)
  Duration: 0:57:07, Preservation Note: High Background Noise During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0324, 718_0542
- A: Religious Fundamentalism with Mark Rosenbloom, Chip Berlet and Azar Nafisi / B: Sept 23 Antiwar Tashlich event; Rabbi Arthur Waskow's Sukkot readings on WTC attacks; Merle Vanderhout on immigrant repression post-Sept. 11 [2001-0166], 2001 October 14; 2001 October 7; cuid34214 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0314)
  Duration: 1:56:15, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Echo During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0538, 718_0558
- Religious Antiwar Responses; Crackdown on Immigrants Post-9/11 [2001-0130], 2001-10-07; cuid34215 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0538)
  Duration: 0:58:05, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0314
- Religious Fundamentalism; Peace Rally Sound [2001-0150], 2001-10-14; cuid34216 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0558)
  Duration: 0:59:36, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Program Recorded at a Very High Level at Times
- A: Jessica Kowal on Bloomberg; Dr. Zia Mian on Islamic Fundamentalism / B: Yuri Avnery, Gush Shalom; Sandi Simcha DuBowski and Rabbi Steve Greenberg on Trembling Before G-d [2001-0165], 2001 November 11; 2001 October 10; cuid34217 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0313)
  Duration: 2:00:35, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0541, 718_0556
- Uri Avnery and Gush Shalom; Sandi Dubowski and Rabbi Steve Greenberg on Trembling Before G-d [2001-0133], 2001-10-21; cuid34218 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0541)
  Duration: 0:59:03, Preservation Note: Digital Errors and Dropouts During Program; Program is Only in Left Channel from 41:55 to 42:24
  Duplicate of 718_0313
- Jael Silliman on Jewish Portraits, Indian Frames, 2001-10-26; cuid34219 (Box 22, Reel 718_0956)
  Duration: 0:25:41, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- A: Ralph Schoenman on Zionism [2001-0179], 2001-11-01; cuid34220 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0326)
  Duration: 2:06:44, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; Static During Program; High Amount of Hiss During Program
- Jessica Kowal on Bloomberg; Zia Mian on Islamic Fundamentalism [2001-0148], 2001-11-11; cuid34221 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0556)
  Duration: 1:00:06, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- Yasser Abed Rabbo of the Palestinian Final Status Negotiating Team; Yossi Beilin, Key Architect of the Oslo Accords [2001-0202], 2001-11-11; cuid35374 (Box 18, Item 718_0675)
- A: Jonathan Rosen and Mohammed Fadel on Anti Arab racism; Jeremy Burton and Angelo Falcon on mayoral race / B: D. Perl and A. Stettner on Murdoch/JCRC honor; Jen Bleyer and Bara Sapir; Nan Rubin interviews Robbie Meeropol [2001-060], 2001 November 18; 2002 February 28; cuid34222 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0309)
  Duration: 1:57:08, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Channel Imbalance; Warble During Program; Echo on Tape
  Duplicate of 718_0536
- Jonathan Rosen and Mohammed Fadel on Anti-Semitism; NY Mayoral Race with Jeremy Burton and Angelo Falcon [2001-0128], 2001-11-18; cuid34223 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0536)
  Duration: 0:58:46, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0309
- Jonathan Rosen on The Talmud and the Internet [2000-0101], 2001-11-18; cuid34224 (Box 21, Reel 718_0947)
  Duration: 0:20:24
  Duplicate of 718_0528
- A: David Kertzer The Pope Against the Jews; Avraham Neguise, South Wing to Zion; Matthew Lazar on WTC death of his uncle / B: Michel Warschawski on bombings in Israel; Sheba Skirball on Sephardic Film Festival; Kathy Goldman on rise in food pantry visits [2001-0163], 2001 November 25; 2001 December 2; cuid34225 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0311)
  Duration: 1:54:48, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0534, 718_0533
- David Kertzer on The Pope Against the Jews; Avraham Neguise from South Wing to Zion; Matthew Lasar on the WTC Death of His Uncle [2001-0126], 2001-11-25; cuid34226 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0534)
  Duration: 0:56:15, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0311
- Bombings in Israel and Haifa; 6th Sephardic Film Festival; Rise of Hunger and Homelessness [2001-0125], 2001-12-02; cuid34227 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0533)
  Duration: 0:58:08, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- A: Aviva Weintraub, Jewish Film Festival, Kathleen Blee with MKK / B: Phyllis Bennis on US Policy on Israel/Palestine, Bob Lederer on Pacifica Board, Alisa Solomon latkes for Hanukkah [2001-053], 2002 January 6; 2001 December 9; cuid34228 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0302)
  Duration: 1:53:59, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Program Recorded at a Very High Level; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0954, 718_0550, 718_0559
- Phyllis Bennis on Bush Stance on Israel/Palestine; Bob Lederer on Pacifica Lawsuits; Alisa Solomon with Latke Recipes [2001-0151], 2001-12-09; cuid34229 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0559)
  Duration: 0:58:34, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0302
- A: Tony Kushner, Alisa Solomon, Tom Segev, Jeremy Barton / B: Chip Bendit on radical right response to 9/11; David Kerner on missionaries and cults and Baptist conversion efforts, Ami Eden on Jewish organizations and civil liberties [2001-0164], 2001 December 23; 2001 December 16; cuid34230 (Box 9, Audiocassette 718_0312)
  Duration: 1:56:07, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0532, 718_0545
- Chip Berlet on the Extreme Right Response to 9/11; David Kerner on Baptist Conversion Efforts; Ami Eden on Jewish Organizations' Lack of Response to Civil Liberties Threats [2001-0124], 2001-12-16; cuid34231 (Box 14, Audiocassette 718_0532)
  Duration: 1:01:58, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0312
- Kathleen Blee on Inside Organized Racism [2001-0205], 2001-12-19; cuid34232 (Box 22, Reel 718_0954)
  Duration: 0:24:19, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times; High Frequency Background Noise During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0550, 718_0302
- Alisa Solomon with Tony Kushner on Homebody/Kabul; Jeremy Burton Interview with Tom Segev on Book One Palestine, Complete [2001-0137], 2001-12-23; cuid34233 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0545)
  Duration: 1:02:43, Preservation Note: Region 1 Was Recorded at 32k; Region 2 Was Recorded at 48k; Program Distorted at Times
- Winter Marathon: Hannah Safran Interview [2002-049], Winter 2002; cuid34234 (Box 22, Reel 718_0965)
  Duration: 0:16:34, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0346, 718_0360
- Jewish Film Festival Sound: 1) "Brownsville Black and White," 2) "The Travellers," 3) "Strange Fruit" [2002-055], 2002-01-06; cuid34235 (Box 22, Reel 718_0971)
  Duration: 0:14:01, Preservation Note: High Amount of Hiss During Program; Static During Program; High Amount of Hum During Program; High Amount of Buzz During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- A: Charles Burton - Fresh Demo; Neta Golan on Situation in Ramallah; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica; Rabbi Michael Lerner on Tikkun conference (Partial) / B: Joe Goldman on the crisis in Argentina; Simon Greer on the World Economic Forum [2002-011], 2002 January 20; 2002 January 27; cuid34236 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0344)
  Duration: 0:58:46, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Echo During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0582
- Charles Barron on Fresh Democracy; Neba Golan on Ramallah Invasion; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica Changes; Michael Lerner on Tikkun Community (Partial) [2002-024], 2002-01-20; cuid34237 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0584)
  Duration: 0:37:27, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- Joe Goldman on the Crisis in Argentina; Simon Greer on the World Economic Forum [2002-022], 2002-01-27; cuid34238 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0582)
  Duration: 0:57:53, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
- A: Jim Hoberman on Sobibor; Kate Rhee and Chino Hardin of Prison Moratorium Project; Wayne Barrett on City Council's choice of Gifford Miller as speaker [2002-015], 2002 February 3; 2002 March 3; cuid34239 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0348)
  Duration: 2:01:38, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0583
- Jim Hoberman on Sobibor; Kate Rhee and Chino Hardin on Prison Moratorium Project; Wayne Barrett on Choice of New City Council Speaker [2002-023], 2002-02-03; cuid34240 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0583)
  Duration: 1:00:53, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0348
- Marathon, Parts 1 and 2 [2002-012], 2002-02-10; cuid34241 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0345)
  Duration: 2:02:30, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0594
- Marathon, Part 3 [2002-013], 2002-02-10; cuid34242 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0346)
  Duration: 0:48:56, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0360, 718_0595
- Marathon Soundcheck [2002-026], 2002-02-10; cuid34243 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0360)
  Duration: 0:50:38, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0346, 718_0595, 718_0965
- Marathon with Andy Hsiao on Legal Lynching; Jenny Romaine and Adrienne Cooper on Anti-Death Penalty Purim Spiel Workmen's Circle; Sasha Abramsky on Hard Times Blues; Hannah Safran on Israeli Activism, Part 1 [2002-043], 2002-02-10; cuid34244 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0594)
  Duration: 1:02:36, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0345
- Marathon with Andy Hsiao on Legal Lynching; Jenny Romaine and Adrienne Cooper on Anti-Death Penalty Purim Spiel Workmen's Circle; Sasha Abramsky on Hard Times Blues; Hannah Safran on Israeli Activism, Part 2 [2002-039], 2002-02-10; cuid34245 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0595)
  Duration: 1:09:26, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
- Marathon with Andy Hsiao on Legal Lynching; Jenny Romaine and Adrienne Cooper on Anti-Death Penalty Purim Spiel Workmen's Circle; Sasha Abramsky on Hard Times Blues; Hannah Safran on Israeli Activism, Part 3 [2002-034], 2002-02-10; cuid34246 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0596)
  Duration: 0:48:48
- Gabriel Meyer Interviewed by Jennifer Bleyer [2002-050], 2002-02-21; cuid34247 (Box 22, Reel 718_0966)
  Duration: 0:11:09, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Dropouts and Warble During Program at 00:01:04
- Robert Meeropol [2000-051], 2002-02-22; cuid34248 (Box 22, Reel 718_0967)
  Duration: 0:30:55, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0487
- Susan Rosenberg [2002-026], 2002-02-24; cuid2618 (Box 11, Item 718_0359, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_616)
  interview with Susan Rosenberg. Never broadcast
- Daniel Pearl Commentary; Andy Stettner on JCRC Honoring of Rupert Murdoch; Jennifer Bleyer Interviews Bara Sapir; Nan Rubin Interviews Robert Meeropol [2002-011], 2002-02-24; cuid34249 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0571)
  Duration: 0:59:06, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Program Recorded at a Very High Level at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0970
- Susan Rosenberg [2002-034], 2002-02-25; cuid35375 (Box 18, Item 718_0680)
- Interviews with Rabbi Marshall T. Meyer Risk Taker Award Recipients: Susan Rosenberg, Dr. Alan Berkman, and Laura Whitehorn [2002-028], 2002-03-03; cuid2610 (Box 16, Item 718_0587)
  Interviews with former political prisoners Susan Rosenberg, Dr. Alan Berkman and Laura Whitehorn, recipients of the 6th annual Marshal T. Meyer Risk Taker Award. Related to 718_0962, 718_0974.
  Original Format: DAT, Duration: 65 min.
- Alan Berkman [2002-045], 2002-03-03; cuid34250 (Box 22, Reel 718_0962)
  Duration: 0:17:14, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0587
- Susan Rosenberg [2002-058], 2002-03-03; cuid34251 (Box 22, Reel 718_0974)
  Duration: 0:16:14, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; High Amount of Buzz During Program
- Bob Gangi on Rockefeller Drug Laws; Parents of Palestinian-Israeli Dead [2002-021], 2002-03-04; cuid34252 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0580)
  Duration: 0:59:08, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0353, 718_0354
- Bara Sapir Interviewed by Jennifer Bleyer [2002-054], 2002-03-05; cuid34253 (Box 22, Audiocassette 718_0970)
  Duration: 0:05:38, Preservation Note: Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0571
- Sherry Gorelick and Nahla Abdo International Women's Day [2002-018], 2002-03-08; cuid34254 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0350)
  Duration: 0:32:48, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Side B is Blank
- A: Zia Mian on 9/11; Michel Warschawski on Israel and Palestine; Jennifer Bleyer and Ellen Lewis on Heeb magazine launch / B: Gabriel Meyer; Redistricting with Jeremy Burton, Sen. Eric Schneiderman and Lucia Goez; Rela Mazali [2002-017], 2002 March 10; 2002 March 17; cuid34255 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0351)
  Duration: 1:56:56, Preservation: Program Distorted at Times; Echo During Program
- Rela Mazali on Her Book Maps of Women's Goings and Stayings [2002-032], 2002-03-16; cuid35376 (Box 18, Item 718_0678)
- Gabriel Meyer on New CD Merkavah; Redistricting with Jeremy Burton, Lucia Gomez, and State Senator Eric Schneiderman; Rela Mazali on Her Book Maps of Women's Goings and Stayings, 2002-03-17; cuid34256 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0358)
  Duration: 0:59:06, Preservation Note: Echo During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0592, 718_0361
- Gabriel Meyer on New CD Merkavah; Redistricting with Jeremy Burton, Lucia Gomez, and State Senator Eric Schneiderman; Rela Mazali on Her Book Maps of Women's Goings and Stayings, 2002-03-17; cuid34257 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0361)
  Duration: 0:58:46, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Side B is Blank; Echo During Program; Program Recorded at a Very High Level
  Duplicate of 718_0592, 718_0358
- Gabriel Meyer with Jennifer Bleyer; Redistricting with Jeremy Burton, Senator Eric Schneiderman and Lucia Gomez; Rela Mazali on Maps of Women's Goings and Stayings [2002-032], 2002-03-17; cuid34258 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0592)
  Duration: 0:56:38
  Duplicate of 718_0358, 718_0361
- Families of the Bereaved at B'nai Jeshurun, Disk 1 [2002-039], 2002-03-18; cuid35377 (Box 18, Item 718_0685)
- Families of the Bereaved at B'nai Jeshurun, Disk 2 [2002-040], 2002-03-18; cuid35378 (Box 18, Item 718_0686)
- A: Ruchama Marton; David Kalick; Kevin Pranis / B: Bob Gangi, Drop the Rock; Parents of Israeli and Palestinian dead [2002-020], 2002 March 31; 2002 March 24; cuid34259 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0353)
  Duplicate of 718_0354, 718_0580
- A: Bob Gangi, Drop the Rock; Parents of Israeli and Palestinian dead / B: Ruchama Marton; David Kalick; Kevin Pranis [2002-021], 2002 March 24; 2002 March 31; cuid34260 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0354)
  Duration: 1:00:16, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0353, 718_0580
- Say No to War, Voices from Israel and Palestine [2002-024], 2002-03-26; cuid34261 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0357)
  Duration: 0:10:47, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; High Amount of Hum During Program
- Voices of Israelis and Palestinians at New Yorkers Say No to War, Part 1 [2002-036], 2002-03-26; cuid35379 (Box 18, Item 718_0682)
- Voices of Israelis and Palestinians at New Yorkers Say No to War, Part 2 [2002-037], 2002-03-26; cuid35380 (Box 18, Item 718_0683)
- Bereaved Families from Israel and Palestine at B'nai Jeshurun [2002-043], 2002-03-29; cuid34262 (Box 22, Reel 718_0959)
  Duration: 0:28:24
- Ruchama Marton on Medical Access; David Kalic on NYC Revenue Options; Kevin Pranis on Lehman Brothers and Prisons [2002-042], 2002-03-31; cuid34263 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0602)
  Duration: 0:57:58
  Duplicate of 718_0977; Related to 718_0600
- Ruchama Marton on Ambulances [2002-061], 2002-03-31; cuid34264 (Box 22, Audiocassette 718_0977)
  Duration: 0:07:07, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Frequency Background Noise During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0602; Related to 718_0600
- Jeremy Burton with Marc Ellis on Practising Exile; Roger Norman on the Israel-Palestine Conflict and Bush's Foreign Policy; Isla Jad Interview [2002-021], 2002-04-07; cuid34265 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0581)
  Duration: 1:00:23, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Program is Only in Left Channel from 01:04 to 02:04
  Duplicate of 718_0973
- Mark Ellis [2002-057], 2002-04-07; cuid34266 (Box 22, Reel 718_0973)
  Duration: 0:16:55, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Frequency Background Noise During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0581
- Ruchama Marton, Eyad El-Sarraj, Mamadou Gaye, and Theo Klein [2002-040], 2002-04-14; cuid34267 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0600)
  Related to 718_0602, 718_0977; Related to 718_0960
- Dr. Eyad El-Sarraj [2002-044], 2002-04-14; cuid34268 (Box 22, Audiocassette 718_0960)
  Duration: 0:08:51, Preservation Note: Broken Splices Repaired; Program Distorted at Times; High Frequency Background Noise During Program
  Related to 718_0600
- A: Stanley Aronowitz and Rob Young, Green Party candidates for governor; Liz Harr and Lincoln Shlensky on student Israel/Palestine activism / B: Bernard Cassen and Mamadou Gaye on Le Pen in French presidential runoff; Marty Rosenbluth on Amnesty International report on Israeli incursions into occupied territory [2002-022], 2002 April 21; 2002 April 28; cuid34269 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0355)
  Duration: 2:01:28, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0568, 718_0588
- Green Party Gubernatorial Candidates Stanley Aronowitz and Rob Young; Elliot Sharpe on End the Occupation Benefit; Liz Harr and Lincoln Shlensky on UC Berkeley Campus Activism [2002-007], 2002-04-21; cuid34270 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0568)
  Duration: 0:58:13, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0355
- Mamadou Gaye on Marine Le Pen [2002-044], 2002-04-25; cuid34271 (Box 22, Audiocassette 718_0961)
  Duration: 0:22:43, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Related to 718_0588, 718_0355
- Bernard Cassen and Mamadou Gaye on Marine Le Pen Victory; Marty Rosenbluth on Israel Incursions Report [2002-029], 2002-04-28; cuid34272 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0588)
  Duration: 0:59:15, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
- A: Gerald Kaufman, MP on his remarks in Parliament vs. Sharon government; Rabbi Drorah Setel, Kadima, Scattle and Jonathan Rosenblum arrested at Anti-Defamation League demonstration / B: Marathon, Part 1 [2002-016], 2002 May 5; 2002 May 12; cuid34273 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0349)
  Duration: 1:54:02, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0598, 718_0335, 718_0589, 718_0976
- Dissenters on Israel: Gerald Kaufman, Rabbi Drorah Setel, and Jonathan Rosenblum [2002-036], 2002-05-05; cuid34274 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0598)
  Duration: 0:56:02, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0349
- Marathon, Parts 2 and 3 [2002-002], 2002-05-12; cuid34275 (Box 10, Audiocassette 718_0335)
  Duration: 1:32:27, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0572, 718_0590, 718_0591
- Marathon, Part 3 [2002-012], 2002-05-12; cuid34276 (Box 15, Audiocassette 718_0572)
  Duration: 0:53:11, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Background Noise During Program; Program is Only in Left Channel from 46:07 to 47:27 and from 48:04 to 53:10; Speed Fluctuations During Program from 46:37 to 47:27 and from 48:04 to 52:36
  Duplicate of 718_0335; Related to 718_0591
- Marathon with Henry Bean, Jennifer Abadi, Jason Sherman, and David Milch, Part 1 [2002-038], 2002-05-12; cuid34277 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0589)
  Duration: 1:07:07, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0975, 718_0349; Related to 718_0335, 718_0572
- Marathon with Henry Bean, Jennifer Abadi, Jason Sherman, and David Milch, Part 2 [2002-030], 2002-05-12; cuid34278 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0590)
  Duration: 1:11:43, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0335
- Marathon with Jason Sherman and David Milch on Reading Hebron, Part 3 [2002-031], 2002-05-12; cuid34279 (Box 16, Audiocassette 718_0591)
  Duration: 0:18:05
  Duplicate of 718_0335; Related to 718_0572
- Henry Bean, Part 2 [2002-059], 2002-05-12; cuid34280 (Box 22, Reel 718_0975)
  Duration: 0:16:14, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0589, 718_0976